Good morning.
Oh, I got a light.
Oh, it's cold.
God, I like, ah, even.
I looked, I didn't see anybody be like, oh.
I was like, it's Friday?
I might go get coffee, stream at five in the morning.
Okay, so I'm out and about,
but it's a little bit cold, it's a little bit.
And I think I like better in this light.
I don't know. It was funny. I met my sister for like, you know, lunch through the night or dinner and she was like,
She's like, you know what? She's like, you look a little scruffy.
Like, after like all I hear about, I look like, you know, just like, I'm just so horrible.
She's like, I look a little scruffy. Like, it's like, you know, she's honest. You can be honest.
So I know, I know kind of like, a little scruffy.
What am I getting? I have this one high sharing good morning. They have some kind of high Nancy
They have some ever hot, honey
biscuit, I don't know. I'm gonna
Make muffin or something. Let me go try that
What's up? What's up? Good morning?
beautiful Rijondo Beach we're passing the
the huge 5g tower
Taking up my coffee
She's a huge 5g. Well, here's a 9-eleven exhibit. Hold on
There's the 5G Tower. See it?
Here's the 9-11 exhibit.
There's actually a really good-looking message.
Like, he had a tattoo on his face,
and he was, like, showing his vision for the...
I don't know, this area.
Yeah, huge 5G Tower.
Looks awesome. Yeah, it's pretty.
This is, um, Redondo Beach Library.
There's Starbucks over there.
This is, like, the little city hall area,
but there's a police station right there.
Oh, no.
At least you are really nice, but they're kind of like, you know, these are kind of like blouse. They they're like, yeah
Yeah, but it is pretty cool. Hey look, you see the golden arches in the head
Said it's ready already. I wonder if I get a delicious
Yeah
There's five for you. Yep. It's really early. I was like, what?
Yeah, we'd write out
And, like, McDonald's is going to kind of add tobacco,
but a little bit on the table to scrape up and back you and stuff.
You know, it feels good.
Okay, good.
Yeah, so we have interesting stuff.
I don't know if you've heard about the sex-cold allegations now.
Yeah.
I watched last night in shock.
You know, try to do a nice thing.
I mean, we have I-N-X. She's like, you know...
I don't know if she divorced or she's a widow.
I'm not sure, but, you know,
when my grandma was like, you know, in her 70s, 80s,
she enjoyed, you know,
she actually ended up with her next-door neighbor.
Oh, yeah, so she enjoyed, like, meeting a man
and said, what happened last night?
Yeah, well, you know, Alexander had a show.
She had, she was spying.
on the official cult activities on my show,
and she saw when I had, you know, Nick Johnson came
in his, like, little bathing suit and was,
remember the tire when he had the trampoline
and had all that rusted metal around him?
Yeah. Well, now Alex is jealous.
I think she never got a stripper.
Well, I thought I was good enough.
I thought me and my speedo.
Sure she saw that.
I can have a carrier, please.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
Look, we got about two profits.
What's that?
Your grandma's earned 104.
Well, congratulations.
Yeah.
Well, my grandma was, I think, like 93.
Oh, thank you so much.
Let's see if I can see the cute.
Where's that guy?
He's kinda cute.
He's kinda skinny.
Yeah.
Yeah, I have breakfast.
104 is amazing.
Um, you know, my grandfather was, I think he was 70s, like it's early 70s when he passed away.
Yeah, that was like a teenager in the 90s, but my grandmother was like, you know, she's like, hey, she's like, she, she like, didn't quite know what to do.
Um, you know, and she was always like telling me, she's like, you know what, she's like, getting old is the worst thing in the world, I hate it, she's like, I did nothing good about it, everything's bad, she's always mad.
She kind of did cool down because she like
Started dating some like, you know older men and my mom is like, you know
I thought like how cute and stuff and then this and then the men's would start dying and stuff
And it would be sad. It would be like all over again. Like she but then the funny thing was
She had these neighbors
All all through this was I I grew up and probably way before
Had their next-door neighbors because they lived in that same house and six, you know for years and years
Um, there's Laura and Vernon and she always be and Laura was kind of like had this, you know
red hair a curly hair and big smoker voice
Alois, you know, and they had this granddaughter and they forgot the granddaughter's name the grandmother was real weird
Like she wanted to sleep my grandma's house
One time and there's he's my grandma had a doll room and so the girl got all scared of the dolls
Had to like leave
But anyway, yeah, and she always wanted to like come watch that movie. She's like, I want to watch hair
As Johnny Depp and she loved that movie. I don't know. So this is some of her kids, right?
But um, so and then you know Laura like we hear stories. Oh Laura like you know, she's a drunk and you know, she fell
She scraped her head. She got finished. She fell on her porch all kinds of stuff
Well, Laura ended up dying and guess who ended up with her next-door neighbor
My grandmother, I mean she and so that's when she passed away
He was like visiting her and stuff that they're both a very very old. They're both in their 90s at the point, you know, and
It was very cute though
His name is burn
my grandma, my grandma was a real cute lady and
She loves to collect capita monte. She loved the home shopping network. She was a doll maker
She was pretty eccentric, you know, but
She was also older than my grandfather. I guess like, you know, she got he was a few years younger than her
turns out but uh, and um, I guess he went to the military or he went to the
Brains of Navy or something. He was some kind of military and sorry grandpa. I don't remember if you were the military. I just remember
but um
Yeah, and so they had like, you know, the baby boomer generation. They had three kids
Yeah, two girls and a boy and
So they grew up my grandma grew up in redondo my grandfather grew up in redondo my
My dad grew up in Glendale
We're almost home. Hey, see I have my in my arms full
Yeah, 104 is awesome. It'd be hard to live, but I saw this Chinese man yesterday. He looked like he was about 200 years old
I mean, it was like the skin was just stretching. He was just a little
ancient
Whoa, they walk you so slow. Oh
They're Chinese medicine must be good because he didn't look that bad, but you look like a mummy, but you know
It's skin was the least a little
hot
Okay. Yeah, so anyway
So then Alexander she then she got I was playing the games or the I night I actually think I
Listen Nick owed me a favor
Okay
So I I got some subscribers one time. So I didn't pay him a
cash
after the show I
Might have put a $5 bill in his thong
that was
private
So, and INX was not interested in that. I'm not trying to sexualize INX
But I think it's cute when people find love. I see I'm like a cupid
Energy like I'm like I'm like also I'm like I'm like I'm like hopeless in love
because of my you know, my mother's Aphrodite and stuff, but you know what I
Make other people fall in love people fall are always falling a little bit around me just never with me
Should I get cursed on a blessing? Okay, so now we're across the street. Okay. I'll be right back. Let me go inside
I'll be sure right there. Who cares. I'm gonna see my
Alexander's like get a magnifying glass you can look at the trajectory of his street posts
Look up the city
Find the exact coordinates of his
location
Yeah, please stop looking at my videos that closely if you are I mean is it
Norca, how are you?
Okay, here we go. We're home. I'm gonna put it. I'm thinking inside. I'm gonna put on my
Nice tonight gosh stream our guests
So we can have a discussion. We'd like to
Maybe I'll play some of her video because she played some of mine. So I'll spare fair
At home I'm right back
This is not mine. This is like just something I like.
I just didn't know what Cal Lakes was.
Fuck boys at the bottle shop after a bathroom ass beating
John Benton, winner pounds of quiet violence
Got you boxed in, angry again
The evil and misty in from these filthy humans
Acting like children, game playing, betrayal and drama
Binging, chameleon, bending and ass kissing
I just rather not let nobody
Just thank you
Driving 3 AM, smoking the fuck
Foking this screw
Bang bang
Don't scream church and let this shit bang
Tanks, kings, swing the patients wide
Then shit the pranks
Now all mums come get me
Hey Si.
Yeah.
Have you ever watched yourself, because I know you rewatch your streams and shit, have
you ever watched yourself eat?
Yeah, you know what, I heard that.
Yeah, okay.
Well, no, so.
I watch you all the time now.
How about this?
Have you ever seen me eat a biscuit?
No, bro. No, I'm good.
Have you heard of the hot honey biscuit for McDonald's?
No, I don't eat McDonald's and if I do, it's very rare.
I very rarely eat McDonald's.
And you can Google McDonald's facts all day long.
It looks just like a regular biscuit.
I mean, show me something special.
Have hot honey on it, right? Okay. Yeah. Yippee. I mean you can buy hot honey at the supermarket
Yeah, bro
No, you know, I'm not gay if I was gay I'd be fucking if I'd talk about sucking dick all the time like you do
I'm not gay, bro. And I don't have a problem with people that are gay
Somebody we both know okay, you know, you're you're allowed on this person to show without your camera
I have my camera. I'm not allowed on the show, but you'll be surprised at what happened yesterday last night
Well ask me about the person real quick before you don't play a clip because I'm at work. I'm just I'm just wait
All right
Form stoic romantic music. He's in the communities and I mean, I know he's all about Moggy jr. Now
I did the book review
Now wait a minute
Okay
Look how young you look back then Jesus dude
So
Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psycho Psych
Better pull this shit off. Huh? I hired you a male stripper because I know you're not gay
I know you want to make I dated a male stripper at LaBear. No, you didn't
Store, okay, so this is supposed to be the male stripper. Let's zoom in. I'm on OBS. So I have full power
Well, I wouldn't want that one
No, I bet if his hair was red she would like Marcus Schenkenberg or
If you listen to Alex, good morning, whatever, but anyway, how come I never got a male stripper, Sharon, when he goes live, ask him why I never got a male stripper.
I would have danced for real.
What do you think?
Who's that?
It's blurry.
Oh, okay.
Let's see the abs.
Look.
I don't know. I saw I saw better apps for strippers to have better apps or they're more her scare. I'll tell you him story
So I'm Karen I and X is not satisfied with this one psych
I'm not satisfied because I never got one, but you're gonna give her one
really
See and you wonder
You wonder certain things
How come she gets one?
But if you sexualize this
Closet lesbian, I'll be impressed
He's a famous actor. He's like a lot of characters. Oh
No, I don't know
It's like getting turned on as this progresses. He's like, what is he doing? He's doing it
for you. Could you imagine ladies going to a strip club with Psycho psych find out a
I don't know what this guy's doing.
Let's see.
What is he doing?
I don't know.
There's looking something here.
Trampoline.
Scrolling down.
I found that video on Alex.
The one that she struck down a year ago.
I found it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let me see.
It's kind of dark there and he was a little blurry.
He's a little blurry.
I'm going to put it close to my home.
Oh, here he is.
I see him.
What's he doing?
He's on a trampoline.
Oh.
He's picking up a tire.
You see him?
Yeah, I see him.
Hey, jump on the trampoline.
Look
Yeah, I'm taking what's happening with my guy Nick Johnson the famous Nick Johnson Nick Johnson's became famous
She jealous like that
I think it goes to everybody page and he works out and that's what he does
Obviously, but yeah, he used to do math. Um skits. He said he should be a skit expert like
You or the skits of movies
Like just out of the day Marcy birthday popped up and he popped up as Marcy. He's a funny guy. He's just
Yeah
You know many times you got dressed up on your page here like I don't get it what you've mad at him for
This is showing a little bit of ab work. Oh come on.
Maybe he was waiting for Wendy's. Remember he was waiting for you.
Come on, eh. Eh, you disappointed me, man.
I thought you were going to go out to the big shots, not the lower class people.
Come on, eh.
Watch a little bit of this with me. Look at her. She's I was watching it. Yeah, that's why I jumped up to get my commentary
I'm not mad at her yo, but that's Nicky Nicky boy Johnson. I'm not mad at her
She could do better. She could do better. She could do better. Come on, girl
If you don't know Nicky by now, you're gonna know Nicky soon
Now I'm gonna send Nicky to her page and then he's gonna be working out doing that over there
Like I heard she was talking about my abs and I'm gonna start showing her
It's a fucking power line right there.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, this is that way again.
Well, that'd be kind of crazy.
I don't want you to get electrocuted on my show.
That would be like.
the power line and what's what's funny about this is you can really sense the sexual maturity level
between um psych and karen aka inx okay i'm gonna tell y'all something that crossed my mind and it
never crossed my mind before but i'm wondering it's quite possible karen aka inx is a virgin
I hadn't even had that thought before but
Considering a few things I know about her
it's a high probability and
maybe
God is working in a mysterious way
by connecting her with psycho psych because
She's an older
at the minimum
bisexual
woman and
If she does have an attraction to men, I mean we know she likes younger men because of
Right
Maybe
She should consider like a threesome with psychocyte and one of his
Dallions that he keeps in his table young stallions
Because they will
Radically everybody god damn. I love my life young why
mentally
um deficient in some way naive maybe a little impoverished they could both
throw him some money I mean we just heard psycho sight say that he bought her
the male stripper I never got one not that I want one I got it no you don't
Well, you're gonna get all right psyche. Let's offer one was I not offer one
Bay clips you
To the audio because you hear psycho psych get
Turned on throughout this and you hear Karen aka INX become increasingly nervous. It's it's crazy
Rusty trampoline full of metal and a big jake right there
You do sit-ups on that trampoline. Wow. Yeah, look at it. It looks it looks a little messy around the edges
I think he already has like hasn't had accidents like that where he's like electrocuted himself. He's like yeah
Yeah, oh so psych acknowledges that this guy is quote-unquote special, but you hear him
Increasingly
It's weird to me like
To understand what I'm saying, but I'm a very sexual person so I do notice
But he's like, he's like a mime, almost, like, oh, more so.
Are you a fan of the mime?
Oh, he's like a mime.
And see, here's the thing about psych.
When he gets turned on.
His voice
Lowers his natural speaking voice is a lot lower than what you normally hear like Michael Jackson
I've said this forever. I don't know why y'all don't pay attention to this, but
site
He's psych is actually naturally a Dom
I'm I've never been convinced that he's actually gay
Bye, I'd have to say bye
But when he's turned on his boys
Yeah
I'm related to the first
Psych is related to the first clown or mime or whatever this is his turn on
he has a
thing
he wants to fuck a clown and
Now if I hear this correctly
If you want to retain the power of psycho-psych you kind of have to you better get ready girl
Yeah, see how lowest voice is getting it. Okay, wait, I'm gonna I'm good
I want all of you to listen to psycho psychs voice
Specifically, okay
because he's really, he's talking to Karen INX about this.
He's drawing her into the sex cult.
What do y'all think cult of psych was?
It's not a joke.
It's the sex cult of the streaming communities.
Why do you think?
He viewed me as such an integral part. Hello. I used to be a porn star
I mean, you know now he's got to find a replacement. It's gonna be INX. Are you ready?
INX Karen to bring the sexy back
To the cult crazy. I don't want you electrocuted on my show
power and she's nervous she can she can sense that the sexual energy starting to raise and I
don't know if Karen can handle I mean she's little mr cat daddy with his uh stable of young buck that
Are obviously available to fuck Karen aka in X fine. It was like a fucking rusty trampoline full of metal
And a big gate right there
Turn the electric fence in two seconds. Wow. Yeah, I look at it. It looks a little messy around the edges
I think he already had like has a hat accidents like that where he's like electric you know, so he's like yeah
They were like special yeah much anymore, but and he likes his young bucks to be special. I
Agree baycliffs. I'm gonna if it lets me I'm gonna put your little comment on the screen. I look we all
Have come to that
Conclusion that's her problem
That's her problem. Okay
She does
That's her problem whenever you see somebody all hyped up and like I gotta keep doing all this stuff to people
It's because they're lacking a sex life
Seriously
He's like he's like a mime almost like a mime or so. Are you a fan of the Miami? Yeah
You know, it's the first cloud.
Hey Nick, we can't see you by frag.
Get on the trampoline with a tire.
See psych psych can't control so looking at this guy
He kind of went back into the falsetto range vocally, but then his voice
Instantly dropped again because he wants to dominate whoever Nick is
Dark again the Champolines are getting close to the camera and flex first
Oh, I want you to I'm paying you know good money for you to like you know get by the next up through
Oh, you're paying good money. Well
How much money and how come I didn't get a male stripper?
That's what I'm wondering
How come after all the time and energy I put in I didn't get even one
Male stripper and Karen out the gate gets one. Thank you psycho psych see look at that
He's gonna give you a thrill
Right. Well, okay. Look what it's done. Oh, it's he's tall though. How tall is he?
He's like so too tall. Damn. He's not seven. Oh, you see that tire? That's a tire for like a monster
truck. Oh, shit. Just roll that around for exercise. It's also sweaty.
Ooh, he gets sweaty.
You know, one time he dressed up like Wendy
from, you know, the Wendy's restaurants.
Yeah, he did.
Yeah.
And then he was like the Wendy's app.
And then one time he dressed up like...
No bakelifts.
I didn't get any gifts.
He said that he gave me gifts.
Well, I guess the AI video,
but I gave him AI videos too.
I didn't get anything tangible.
No, that's why he could not be the will to my grace
No, no, I I I only
Hetero or LGBTQ
I've decided that I only want men around me who are gonna give me some cool gifts because I give cool gifts
So, you know, I'm starting to value myself more and whatnot and you know, it's like psycho psych
He's too flugel for me. Dr. Pepperica, I guess
He doesn't drag
Oh, he looked a little bit like
thing that is. Everybody's crushing on thing that is and
thing that is he's on vacation and I think Cancun or Mexico or
whatever right now. But are you telling See, I've I've
suspected this for a while. It's psycho psych having a fling
with thing that is
Is that why thing that is, is always on Psycho Psych's panel?
No.
What's really going on here?
Cap on, he was like talking to Ralph.
I think I had to end it at some point.
But, you know, he's like, if you watch back and he's like,
okay, he was trying to communicate something.
I don't know if it's, does he need help?
Does he?
I don't know.
He's scared.
He's like, he just doesn't talk anymore.
Nick, can you come talk to us for a second?
Yeah, come talk what I next wants to ask you a question. Look. Oh, I nice look at them
Okay, no, I didn't want to well, let's get a look at Nick up close. Let's use the power of OBS. I
Mean if he's mentally impaired I
Don't tend to do that, but I mean
From this angle, he reminds me of vegan patriots Justin a little bit.
Doesn't this remind you of Justin?
Oh, this is fun.
He is hilarious.
Yeah, it reminds me of Justin, but Justin, he was a little mentally impaired.
Sorry, Justin. But you are. Let's keep watching. Ask a question. Just ask him something. I mean. Oh, okay. You're asking. I don't have a question for him.
Ask INX something. What do you want to know about INX? Anything you want to ask? I don't have anything to ask. Why don't you have anything to ask?
INX I mean if you're gonna wield the power of the psycho psych you got to get on board with the sex freak train
What?
You're not willing to have a freak off with this fine young possibly special young buck
Hands selected for you by psycho psych
He's gonna drop you if you don't get on board with a freight train. Please come or get with it, bitch
I don't know who he is. Oh, you don't know who he is. Well, you're gonna find out
See, he's exercising
He's right. Nothing. I don't know him. I don't have any questions psyche. I don't I don't know the guy
Oh
So what if you don't know
Yeah, you're asking the questions. I don't know him
He's ignoring me. Now he's gone back to flipping that time.
Probably busy because he's doing the, what is he doing?
He's working, oh, okay, he's picking up stuff.
I think he's trying to like go to the store, but it's like, okay, so.
No, he's not going to the store.
He's exercising for the freak off that's coming up.
Okay, let's see, let's skip ahead, okay.
He said, oh, noble, I say hi to noble too.
Noble who's noble? He's a like a Mexican guy. Oh, there's somebody else or with him. It's kind of dark
What you like what like what is this you want to get your freak on and like sterile light
Now it needs to be a little bit damn
How long has it been since you've been intimate?
I and X Karen because we're gonna find out this was just day one. I
Know what psycho Sykes plan is for you
Do you know?
Yeah, oh good ones too from California
I got kind of don't know these days. Oh, these are powerful. I'm getting hybrid sativa and
And what was the other one indica
Indica kind of strong and some gummies feel like this is like a couple bags that'll last a while
I wanted to play this the other day with you. I have a game show
Oh, you want to play with ianx now
Wait a minute. Let me rewind. Wait a minute. Is he on video on this? No, he's not. He's
back. He's jacking off while he's talking to INX, you know. See, I'm going to be careful
You know how Pee Wee had his playhouse?
This is Psycho Sykes Playhouse, these communities.
I have figured that out.
Listen to what he says.
I'm going to rewind it.
Listen, just really listen.
Morning babes.
He's like a baby.
Oh, good ones too from California.
I got kind of stoned off these days. Oh, these are proud from getting hybrid sativa and
Oh, yeah
And what was the other one indica?
Yeah, I love it indica kind of strong and some gummies
A couple bags. I mean, they're smoking, eating gummies,
watching this guy throw it a towel, a tire around shirtless.
Look, I think INX and PsychoPsych are gonna end up being the most
interesting content for the rest of the year. It's gonna be like nothing but, um...
Well, I'm not gonna say because I could be wrong.
But I don't think I am.
He's gonna sexualize the hell out of her.
Ooh, it's gonna get crazy.
Little after a while.
I wanted to play this the other day with you.
I have a game show.
So it's a very game on my website.
And it's like, you know, it's playable on this.
Right.
See how it looks today.
Okay, let me see if I can get a game show.
And that should be.
Ready to go. Okay. It is. Oh, it's ready to go. It's a game show. I didn't get any game shows
Seeing I made the right move and disconnecting from him. I didn't get any male strippers
I didn't get any game shows. I didn't get any of this shit
Yeah, that's why I left the cult
Frickin' stingy, frugal, cheap ass.
Yeah, like Capricorn.
That's what we are.
Wanna be pimp?
Okay, it's ready to go.
Okay.
We are pimp.
So, you are the contestant.
You can win up to a lifetime membership on the Colt Codex.
I had to buy my membership.
She's just gonna win it?
And I left him.
Which will give you also, like, you know, correct.
the protection and whatever. Okay, so here we go.
Protection?
So, um...
Man, a little grisky.
Protection for the live.
Welcome to the game show. We have INX in the studio.
See? See?
You see how these, uh, streamer scam artists are?
I didn't get any of that.
I didn't get any of it clap tokens. Yeah, I've heard I heard I heard about the clap tokens
So anyway, I just wanted to share that I just wanted to
Me like fucking she I call her for fucking help, you know, she knows like you hear you're on the disability
Right? So she fucking, she's here all day. So like if I'm gone, like I can, she has my back. She watches my shit, you know what I mean?
Yeah, I want to walk. Hey, I want to wash your back. Where you came? So Chris, hey, were you ever in a bath with OJ, OJ geezer?
What was that picture where you were naked in a shower with them?
I mean, that's that's AI, bro. Hey, clumsy, what a bunch of, hey, come up.
But you have had showers with men, right? Like
In jail. Yeah. Yeah. Were they fun?
Well, what do you mean in jail like you don't shower with men it's separate showers. Oh, I shower with men in jail
Yeah, but it's not a communal shower. Yeah, but in Boston, maybe we're there. So
Like there's no next like there's no individual doors like it's open, but
First I take a shower with like 15 Mexican guys and then I take a shower with
What do you mean? It was one big open communal shower?
Yeah, well that was the first one where everyone, when we got processed in, everyone took one,
they make it one take one, and then it's like when you're out in the peckerwood wing,
then at the peckerwood they would say, oh come take a shower with us, and it was like one shower.
Three guys in one shower.
It didn't happen like that. They'll be like a designated shower where all the stuff goes.
It was great. I loved it.
And like, you know, there's no doors, so everybody's trying to swing their packers around and show them.
Yeah, everyone wants to show them. Oh, and NorCal's been to L.A. County. Okay, let's see.
I want to hear some deals.
You guys have never been to prison before?
No, not prison, just county jail.
This guy's never been
Actually much better than I'm never I've never been to jail. I've only ever
When I get arrested they don't even send me to jail. They just send me straight to prison
Right in the peak. Oh, you're a bitch nigga
What a website
What's up? Yo, yo Chris, I'm happy for you got yourself some pussy nigga. I'm happy for you nigga
I'm happy for him too. He's so cute. Hey, so Chris. So the peckerwood peckerwood. So now you have this gay guy and he's jealous now. Okay, so basically Christian winning. All right. You're the hot guy on the town.
She had to go to the bathroom, I guess, you know.
Okay, she has to go because, you know, okay.
Well, Chris, now we can get to business.
So tell me more about your pocket pussy.
Well, yeah, I used to show them, like you can go on,
you can actually go on YouTube and look up,
fucking, you know, device and like it.
Now, what race is the vagina ass piece?
Like what is that, Mexican?
It's white.
It's a white one.
Is it just pure white, or is it like a real white skin?
It's it's like silicone, but it's like, you know, it's white. Yeah, it's like the first time you used it
I would you tell me tell me the scenario so you're watching a movie
I haven't I haven't used it like literally probably in like a year, but like you need I mean you don't need Chris
Can you show it like come on show it? I can't but I'm not trying to do it with the with my friends here, so
Okay, we gotta be careful boys. Yeah, some of them might want to look at it
You got all three I want to see how the mouth is connected to the butthole and
Who the fuck is that creature right above me?
That's Mike Strokoff.
I don't know.
I don't want to see it.
It's a cereal.
Rope gang.
Rope gang, ay-oh!
Rope gang!
I gotta look at Keith's teeth.
Okay, we're well KZ. I think you showed a picture of his scuff teeth. Oh my god
Nigga, do you want me if you don't fuck her tonight you're a bitch
White my ass and get a pair underwear and I'll go outside. Hold on a second KZ. I got you bro. Give me a second papa
Give me a minute. Give me a minute.
Listen, if you don't fuck with me tonight, you're a bitch.
He's sick. He's sick. He's sick.
Hey, Norfowl, shut the fuck up and go lay some more tiles for me, bitch.
You're an angel.
They say you're a Mexican nigger.
Hey, hey, I'm going to knock out the air force.
Oh, so, is that the N-word?
Are you okay, Papa?
I'll just say it real quick.
No, look, look.
SIG's not black. It doesn't count.
Pay attention. Pay attention.
I don't think I've called one dark man
the N-word. I think it was Ron,
Alter Ego, so
it was well deserved,
in my opinion.
But I digress and I kind of I'm kind of fucking I kind of like Ron right now for some fucking weird reason
But I'll tell you what I'll do
I'd knock every one of you motherfuckers out with one punch because you're all weak as shit, especially you
especially
You guys get my humor now you get I knock I'm just one I'm not even a uppercut
Just a I'd slap the fucking breath out of all your fucking throats
Especially you age-rigging Creech right over to my right you fucking
Hiv-ridden creature
Bro jokes banter
I say you have AIDS, say I'm fat, fuck it.
Joker finally has-
Say I fuck black women, because I do.
No, I mean, listen, you don't even come up
so Mike's taking pictures.
Yeah, no, no, that dude's spoke joke was funny.
Mike's broke off your piece of shit.
That was funny.
He spoke joke about assholes.
You know, psych, you should be an expert at assholes.
You've never been to LA County jail, pussy.
You liar, Mike.
You ain't been to nothing.
You're a whole county bitch.
You ain't done shit.
You would have been a protective trustee with all the other fucking creatures like T-Matthews.
Oh yeah, I sucked all the dicks.
Well yeah, he definitely would be because...
I was a trustee, I was a trustee.
They always put people like that in PC whether you want to or not.
I was a misdemeanor, I was on PC, you were a PC fan.
Well no, I'm saying like you were a trustee, right?
Yes.
I wore blue, I wore blue, I worked in the kitchen.
I was there for like T.A.
Back to my point, you know?
Yeah.
Like they didn't have to worry about you.
Hey, is that the same NorCal from fucking, from Twitch?
That's all I want.
Yeah, I'll bring him up.
I'll bring him back.
Well, is he the same one that was in Annie Melanakis's?
Yeah.
No, dude, dude, come on, psych, don't be a pussy.
Dude, I barely, we barely even got going.
If you want to be a part of IPQ,
if you want to be a part of the IPQ communities,
let me go ahead and break you in.
Let me break you in.
Let me break you in like a real faggot
would break in somebody at prison inmate.
Dude, you're fucking balls and penis of shrunk
since I've met you.
Hey, Norco, you're fucking drunk, it's small now.
Hey, Elda, what up?
What up, what up, psych, man?
What up, man?
You caught the Vicky versus Bita, right?
You know what I'm saying?
Bita turned on Vicky now.
Yeah, I was there in the chat part.
Elda, why are you got the picture?
Hey, I got it all spread.
Come on, Chris K, why you got your moms on the screen?
Come on, Chris.
Come on. I got it all spring out.
Come on, man. Come on, dawg.
I caught that, Tom.
That's true. I'm Chris.
Vicky, we're going at it.
Go for me.
Hey, Pazza.
Let me go, man.
Hey, Pazzo, wait.
They want to say hi to you.
Chris, that's your mom.
You don't like her?
Hola, senora.
They want to say hola.
Another...
Ciderita.
Oh, she is spending?
Got to spend it?
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK
What up bro? Like you know homie dog, I love you dog.
I love you too.
Let's get a place together dude.
Oh my god, he's gonna move in with me.
It's gonna play some talent.
I know what you said.
I'm on Psyche. I bested Nordkau. Psyche, come on man.
Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche, Psyche.
I can't even get any deads.
I feel like...
There's something there, there's something there.
You're like, where did you take me?
Stay from your chair.
Oh no, take me away from there.
I'm trying.
Oh my god.
I'm confused. I think that's his voice.
It's not his voice.
I got...
You said...
I don't want to say no one.
You will need one?
What is it?
Muy bien.
Muy caliente.
Un poquito.
Esa es muy borracho.
Bueno.
Fuck you, you know me like, uh, you know fucking bottle locals forever. You know me
It's just you clean your house. Yeah, I might I'm my job psyche job. The link psyche
You know me
If we know each other, I don't know you.
No, I don't know if I'm real live.
This is fucking internet.
Idiot, don't fuck yourself.
I want to get caught hanging out with Scythe.
She just said your real name, Crisco.
Don't get mad.
She called you Matthew.
Thank you.
Who called me, man?
Oh, my god.
Do I want to be my boyfriend?
Pia, I'm going to introduce my boyfriend to you guys.
You're a short boyfriend.
What the fuck?
No boyfriend.
Show us, folks.
Baby.
Full screen.
There you go.
It's like we did with B to pull your panties in.
Bag it.
It's the same man.
Look, it's the same man.
Play it touching.
It's the same man.
Look.
Oh, my God.
Hey, look, you know, y'all look like what's that guy from Canada to beat a likes what's
that guy's name?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Yeah, you guys have a boat on us.
Let's go fishing.
That's a lake right there.
I don't want to get on the boat.
I don't want to rip off it.
There was a really good reading after work.
I don't know if they call back in or something.
I don't know if I don't have it, it'll have it.
I wanted to see the Chris K. reading.
Chris K. had that earlier several hours later.
Yeah, so it's this one.
Guys, do you want to see?
So this is the INX Chris K. reading.
We're trying to talk about what happened as she's doxing and everything.
Okay, so anyway, she was going to go live and she was going to tell she was in Florida
right across the street from them at a restaurant and she was already drinking.
So I feel like I talked to you before.
I don't think so.
I think I've seen you up before, but I don't think we really talked.
fucking book, you know, he made an AI picture of with the Pekingese. I've grown up with
Pekingese dogs. And he put a lava behind it. That's an AI Pekingese. So that's not my Pekingese
to, like you said, I don't know who the fuck Michael is, Mike. I dated a guy named Michael,
but I also have a cousin in England. His name is Michael. Yeah, something. Let me get
Hold on. Just two, just two. We've got the buster. Well, you have like pets, right?
Yes, I do. I have four rescues and a show quality pecanese.
Okay, so they are, but there's one that's like the mother or something?
Well, she's not a mother, but she I call her the bully cat because she's jealous of other cats
But she's kind of acting like the mother to the new kitten that I took in that was rejected by its mother
So she's being real good with her
You're like to pass it, you know, obviously yeah, but there's a I don't know where you live
You know, but you uh, are you like uh, you're like you're single. I am now. Yes
But I mean, I you know, let me I'm just gonna say it. Can I say it? I was married once but no not after that
You know, you fantasize about you know, like penis
No, I don't
Okay, I'm sure yeah, I'm not yeah. No, there's somebody that you wish you had that used to be flowers
Whoever that was somebody that let me write. No
No, mm-hmm. No
I don't care for flowers. I was never went into like in caring
You ever got flowers that yes, I did and I just got some recently for my birthday
Okay, how long from a friend here? Who was that?
It was my best friend and her mom
Okay, well these those others were just gifts gifts from other people. They're fucking uh, they're fucking jokesters, right?
I wouldn't say they're jokesters.
You're my best friend is sometimes,
but it was her mother that got the flowers.
Yeah, she messes with you.
Not really.
She's a really nice person
and she doesn't speak any English.
But she has like some, she also has a pet, right?
Yes, they also have some rescues to some cats.
But they're like, they're like good or something.
They're very good people, yes.
and animal lovers.
It means to go back here.
You got mustard, or like you fucking shit.
You have a, like I said, you have a sister, right?
Yes, I do.
Okay, you're fucking, I don't know what your dad is always,
your dad is always like fucking like,
telling you to like fucking,
you have more potential that you're not using it.
He did when I was doing drugs, when I was young.
Cause he's trying, he wants to help you,
but you're like standing there.
Not doing it
Yeah, not doing it because I wouldn't listen not till later
Then I ended up going to college and you know got a job graduated and all fucking what you know
You have like so much potential and you're just like, you know, please
Yeah, I did waste a lot of it when I was doing drugs. I did
But you know, you're dead. You're dead. What the fuck up you? Oh, come on asshole
Psyche what do you have this bitch over here Psyche? Get him off. I got I got
Coins Psyche
You know, this is fucked up the Psyche. Let's that asshole in like he thinks it's funny
That's that salmon that gay guy the guy that that doesn't have he lives in section 8 and fat and ugly
Yes, salmon that full of fuck is racist like
See get him out get him out. Why did you let him on psyche? Why do you do this?
Yeah, don't don't let him on he's a little piece of shit he lives with his dad
I have I'm gonna put that video up to where his dad's yelling at them
They live in a section 8 room and you saw the picture and he's afraid of men
Because when they go at him, he disappears.
You're afraid of men, Samman?
He's afraid of men.
Yeah, he is.
He's a fucking weirdo, man.
He doesn't even have a job.
He was given his food stamps to KK, lied, and when it heard a lie to say that he had
an Audi and he was going to go pick her up, they never met.
And so all his information and pictures are out there.
You want to see his mom?
No, I'm not gonna show you right now, but yeah, I got all that stuff because even I don't mean I don't like him
But I won't because he was he once said that Alex was wrong for my parents and so I'll just say Sam
And I'm not gonna try to go after his to see his loved ones or like let anybody else do it
Like you know, but you know, he should just know I do have his back like sometimes, you know
It's like he should maybe like
I'm in the middle of it, like fucking the, you know,
let me just get through it.
This shit fucking, I don't know if you had, like,
somebody, I don't know what it is that they get hurt,
like, somewhere like one of your family members
or something, like your friend.
Hurt as in what, just-
I don't know, they got upside down or something?
No, no, nobody, uh-uh.
Well, I did at age three, I did at age three, I did.
I almost lost my life at age three.
But nobody and nobody else in my family
So you you assist you and your sister like you guys like this this person was a musician
What I was I wasn't played it in a guitar trumpet when I was young
She played a piano you idolize some somebody both you guys
Right. Um, damn. Yeah. Um, God, who was it a David Cassidy when I was a little little kid
Like a violin, what the fuck is that? No, nobody in my family played a violin guitar
Okay, maybe it's guitar like but you and your sister like are both you both like this person
It's like musician Beatles like you're like, oh, it's my favorite. I want to go to a concert, you know
Yeah, sometimes we have you know, it's not but it wasn't the one we both had a crush on well
Sometimes you know when we're little kids when we'd have a crush on a who are a pop star or whatever
No, not at all
But she's not into that type of music
Me and my younger brother are he knows he knows him. So he gets free tickets. That's it
No, never she used to be a model, but no, there's no plastic surgery in my family
You know anybody that has like plastic surgery no nobody
I'm sure no, I don't know anybody that had plastic surgery
Regular but no plastic surgery. I mean, I mean how big your teeth
They're just a medium size maybe like a 32 32 not you know 34 32 not it's 32. It's you did. It's you you're the moment the titties, bro
Well
I mean you can't cam up we can't see what you look like. Um, I have but I'm not gonna cam up here because there's a lot
Of assholes here though, so I don't do that. I'm not I'm not a public figure and I'm not a streamer
So yeah, I do on on private like on phone or IG, but not on YouTube with all this shit
You you fucking know you'd like to get your titties out
No, I don't I'm not like
You fucking you're always like, you know
with them or something like that. I don't know. Let me just go in here.
So you are okay. Let me fuck. I don't know what it is with uh like I said your father your father
was like uh love both both you and your sister equally and he talks a lot your dad talks a lot
and uh it's it's wild uh I don't know is he like uh
He's not white, right? Yes, he is. He's English and Scottish. Yes, his mom was Scottish and my
His dad was in English. He's very white green a blue green eyes
Blondish brown hair. Okay, but you know he
Something with an Asian is he no nothing. No, he was he was a racist pretty much
My mom my mom is part span is Spanish and German well
I see like you know like you know Indians put like you know like base paint or something. No, nothing. No, he's very white
No
He liked the western movies cowboys and Indians and you know, I'd watch them with them when I was a little kid
That's you know closest thing to to that
So I
You say you don't do it, but I guarantee you like
I mean, you're wearing it in your face paint, Karen.
Where did you wear it?
No.
He sees you in the paint.
Maybe it was past.
Well, there's like some scenario that you have in your head.
There's a scenario that you have when you master it.
Oh, no.
End of story.
Well, I don't think so I've been well. I'm getting older though, too. So no
No, I mean did you like you like it's like on a beach like on the sand like I never did that on the beach when I go
To the beach I'd go swimming or tan. That's it. I never did anything like that on the beach. I had sex in the beach before
Yeah, you like miss that you you fantasize about that, right?
I don't fantasize about it. It happened and and it was you know, it's it's I was uncomfortable because you know
That's public public beach. So I didn't like it my boyfriend did then we did it a couple times
right and he uh
Was it with this guy? What is it with this guy?
What's that with that guy almost all his name is it like some of the J
With the G and oh John. Yes. That was my recent X. Yes, John
Should I go through real quick, but uh, and hold here and it starts with a J
Yeah, some of the J and you like, you know, you you know, I'm just going off your shit
You'd like this is what you know, you bet you let you you think about this when you
when you you know, so
Listen, and this is why I hate doing this bro because people fucking I get down to it and they're like they've this nope
I don't do it. I'm on stream. I don't want to like announce it to everybody
you know no i'm telling you the truth about that yeah yeah like i'm not lying dude you know i mean
this is what's going on like fucking me you know i mean so yeah and everybody's like no you're wrong
you're wrong i don't want to be known for that so they don't fucking they don't lie they lie oh no no
there's no no to those you know but the beach do you have a few times with the in it i hate to see
i hate this but you know i don't go out there and do all this shit in pro in public now
Just that time.
I don't know where you live, but I don't know if you want to.
You're trying to move, maybe?
Yes, yes.
I am thinking about that.
Yeah, me too.
But there's a problem.
You have, like, do you have a snake, a reptile?
No, I don't like snakes.
I'm scared of snakes.
Well, I don't know if it's a snake,
but like, do you have a problem?
Do you want to make sure that you can bring your pets?
Um, I have cats in a pecanine. So no, I don't worry about snakes or where I live
There's no snakes or anything like that. I'm kind of scared of snakes. So I don't like snakes. I know you you've had bad experiences
I don't know. It's something that with this chick that I'm
Fucking I don't want it with any like an Indian chick that you got upset with a snake
No, I didn't know any Indian people, but I had a neighbor that lived next door and he had those big snakes
What do you call them the boa? What the big ones Burmese python? Yeah, yeah, that's what it was. Yeah
And I was concerned about his dog. He had a dog and it's like damn when you leave
But you're sure about leaving him with the snake because you know you hear about these accidents
But nothing happens. I would worry about that. He literally fed a snake like bunnies like rabbits
Yeah, I heard that, you know, or mines or rats
There's somebody that you know, maybe so I don't know if it's on here. I doubt it's on here
but like there's somebody that's fucking a super uh
Like makes fun of you. Like I said, I thought it was maybe like
That was like uh, it's like uh, do you do do you do like a trying to yoga or something?
No, I've never done yoga, but maybe I'd like to learn it, but no, meditation, yeah, meditate.
Well, I know it's yoga, but like, you know, you're like afraid to go to the gym?
No, I like going to the gym.
Well, that's what it is. I think somebody there is like...
Well, I'm joining a new gym. The one that I used to go to, they moved way out too far away.
It's really far, so I'm looking for another one nearby.
There's there's a lot of fucking like
These people that are like they fucking are like, you know, I don't think it about you or like whatever
So I'm sure I try to I think I got that that's basically it
I'm trying probably because like when I got sick I ended up in the hospital last year and
You know, they were worried about me because I was gone for a while and now that Jim moved
I was in a physical rehab facility. They did have a type of like a rehab type of gym. So I worked out there
Yeah, they were worried because I didn't think I didn't think I was gonna make it or I'd be there a long long time
Wait, what happened? Why'd you have to go to that?
I just got sick. I wasn't my right liver didn't get enough water and I'd be doing like four
formal runs in the middle of the heat and you know I almost had a heat stroke one time. I wasn't
being careful and I started getting sick and then I wasn't eating and I just got really sick to where
I couldn't even get up one time and I wasn't paying attention to doctors and taking the medication.
And I ended up and I see you I was there for a week and then I ended up in the physical rehab
They had me in a wheelchair first. I couldn't even sit up, but I made it through
I was there like two months and I got better and then then I was out. So I'm doing great
You're like you're like on disability, right?
No, no not on disability because I'm fine now. So no, I was there the whole time. So no not disability
You're trying you're trying to get on it
You know what I asked somebody about it, but no I can't get it because I've got a 401k plan and my parents money or whatever
So no and I made a lot of money though, too
So I couldn't I asked somebody about it that they were on it and there's no way that they give me that plus
I'm fine now because I didn't know if I was gonna be on a walker for a while
You know because when I got out of that facility
They told me I had to still use a walker for a while and I did until November
And so I'm better now. So they're surprised, you know, they said I was pretty much a miracle.
I'm actually going back to work in September, the job that I had, but I'm wanting to move though.
But you're concerned about something something to do with animals. You're concerned like that's your me
Yeah, my concern is taking them because I was thinking I
Support a rescue group in Indonesia and they do a lot of great work
And I have them on my IG and I talked to them and they thanked me for the donations over the help
And I was thinking that
you know, if I retire or maybe before that, I'd like to just go over there and they say,
great, maybe you can come join us. They wanted to give me a dog and I said, well, I'm here in the
state. So I was thinking about going over there, but then I'm concerned about the pets that I have
now and my dog that take them over there because I've never moved to another country with pets
So I worry about that. Yes. Yeah. That's what that's what's holding me back. I don't know. I don't
know if that's that's holding me back. Yeah, because it's like what happens if I move to this
strange country by myself and my pets, you know, and you're a big pet person. You know what I mean?
Yes, I am all my life.
Look actually my cat. Oh really? Yeah. Oh my god. See they're so cute
Khaleesi her name is Khaleesi
Khaleesi. Yeah, I need to find a name for one of these cats. I'm just calling boy cat and he's all very vocal
I don't give her watch the Game of Thrones
I've seen it before. Yeah
That's I mean my mom my mom named the cat. She was a big fan of the you know the dragon king queen
So that's where
Yeah, like I'm sorry just like I mean seriously like you uh
Well, I mean you like you're like horny
No, I'm not really. I'm not I guess as you get older. You're not the horny like that anymore. No, I think you are you like you like
No, I'm always thinking about this person on the ocean like you know like on sand
No, not at all that was years ago
So I don't even think about that. I don't even think about him. We were young. I wouldn't do that now go out there
Well, it's your fantasy and you also let you something to do with your mouth and then
Oh my god, I mean it's all good. I'm not
You don't want to meet up
Okay, I guess like you were you did you leave again or
Do a reading on Psyche. I've never seen, you know, seen somebody do a reading on him.
You're doing this, so I'll have to get it next time for you to come.
Oh baby, you're so cute.
You're a cute cat.
Yeah, the little baby out there.
I see the young one.
I say it as I see it, you know.
Are you playing? You got your cat?
Yeah, they're right here with me.
I just took in a baby cat that the mama rejected.
Hey, calm up. Let me see.
I'm not gonna come up right now. I'm practically in bed, man. I'm sunburnt. I was out in the pool today got really hot 100 degrees
So I'm here killing with my babies. Where you live at?
I'm not gonna give my address. I'm in Texas. Take I'm in Texas now. Yeah, I live right near the beach
Yeah, the closest one here is Galveston I'm joking I live in Vegas
Oh, really? Vegas? I've been there before. It's beautiful.
He is. He is.
I've been here five years. I'm a youngster.
This is my youngster.
Where are you going to move to?
Right near the beach.
Oh, wow.
The only thing I worry about is living by beaches, hurricanes,
especially here.
Well, I think about Florida, which is the hurricanes, right?
Yes, I know. I was a little kid when we lived there, Coral Gables, Miami. I lived in West
Africa and South Africa, too. A lot of places overseas in Nigeria. I think Alex has an accent
like she's Nigerian, but you know, you know. So, yeah.
There's no kings there in the euro. She said the evil tribe
They have a king. No, there's they live in the slums by the airport
Is your dad your dad have a like something with this like breathing that's this they messed up or no with what?
It's like reading like air
No, not at all. No
He lived a long time. He died at the age
You know, he was he lived a long time and he was pretty much healthy and
And then he got Alzheimer's
That's what it is. He was 80 years old. He got Alzheimer's at 80
Nobody in our family's had it, but I think his dad had it
Not really he was kind of quiet man, I mean so he was in that talk that I was like my mom was she was
Think about and see what he looks like almost in his name
What what is your what is your the first letter Jay for Jim?
Well, you just tell me oh my god, you were gonna say the name
But I mean he gave you you and your sister like something's like, you know, whatever something like well, they left us money
Him and my mom and she had more because of her family
Your dad was you that was cool dude like he was cool
He could be cool like with his friends and stuff. So yeah, he was you know, but he'd be an angry band sometimes so
He was very smart not not an asshole, but like he was like strict strict, you know, yes, yes, he was
which is cool, and you talked a lot.
I mean, we got to travel the world pretty much because of him.
He worked for a major oil company,
so we lived everywhere overseas,
and first class always, you know.
All the time. It was yeah, it was a beautiful life, you know traveling and
Offshore or no no an old company like in countries and and then in the summers
We got nice free vacations all summer long to any place we wanted to so
We that's what I enjoyed there, you know, you made hell of it
Yes, he did mobile oil company. That's who he worked for so he had a high position there and nice and get transferred around a lot
He was a good guy dude
He was very smart though, and he was a hard worker
Yeah, and then you know he's trying to he's trying to help his family to help you guys
Yeah, we had some beautiful vacations, you know, we went on beautiful vacations for him
You know, I was almost like I'm almost
Sad for for you
No, I enjoy that I just I just didn't like those long plane rides going overseas, you know 12 hours 17 hours
I didn't like that
We're looking out the window especially at night time and I'd hear the seat the waves crashing
And I thought those were like whales waiting for us to crash and and for them to eat us
Yeah, you got like red red red everything. Mm-hmm. That's cool. I fucking he's a he was a guy, you know, mm-hmm
I can almost I can almost like do one for him
Do one on Psyche. I want to know. I never seen Psyche get a reading because he's done some readings
Like your dad, you know, he misses you he misses you
Yeah, I don't know you have the last time I saw him. Yeah, I think I think so. It's like
Yeah
There's some stuff you didn't you gonna get to tell you
Yeah, that's true. I found that out later that yes, but you know, he hugged me and all before he passed away
I'm not trying to do this
You know
What is psyche though he leaves his show all the time psyche were you at?
Sorry, it's like there's a lot of good people do that like
They didn't get to say what they wanted to say you know
Yeah, and that's true
And I wish I was there to hear him out because he said it to my youngest sister and brother
For me and they didn't even tell me that tell me until after he passed away
So I felt kind of bad. It's like maybe I needed that talk with them. So I regret that
Always working. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Yeah, I mean basically uh
That's basically it. Yeah, you had a cool dad dude. Your dad fucking is the man and uh
My mom was great though. She had the personality. She was loved by everybody and she had a great sense of humor
In a very contagious laugh. Hey listen don't let anybody fucking know when you like when you're at the gym like fucking fuck them dude
They're trying to like talk shit, you know me?
No, nobody in the gym has ever talked shit ever had any problems
I gotta join a new one now because that one like I said moved to I went they moved far almost
Like I don't you know, I don't think you know this I don't think you know this
They skinny boat Jones over here fucking doing well right now. Yes, I did lose too much weight and that's kind of embarrassing
So yeah, and I got to keep up with the water too
And I was like that when I was a kid, you know, they practically tried to force me to eat
But I didn't think I was skinny. I've got a lot of pictures, you know, and they said oh you were skinny and
Well, I wasn't but I do get fat for like three years about ten years ago and that's gone
But I guess I lost a little too much now
I don't know what it is like there's a lot of people that
Like they fucking like joke on you like fucking that they make jokes about you. You know me so
Right. No, that's Sam and now using an old fat picture of me when he's fat himself and dumpy look in and won't show face
He's a screamer, but refuses to show face. I mean, I'm not internet
No, that that that's the only one like that that's all in real life. No
No, but I was worried because um, you know, I ended up like I said, I was in
You know, this was a year ago and then my brother heard I guess it was Alex that reached out to him
He said a lady from wiki info
Contacted him and said I was buddies with Larry the meth head and I said I don't know who Larry is
I said there's a lady that they call amber meth head and I said who told you that and he said a wiki info
and he said that she said you did meth and that is that why you lost all more weight and all and
you know he started accusing me of doing meth I said no I got sick you know and just talked to my
doctors so I blocked him but when I was discharged I went straight to their place to confront him the
next morning because he was pissed and when he saw me he seemed relieved I said look at my face
I said, why don't you talk to my doctor and don't worry about it.
Yeah, and then he was right.
And then he seemed relieved and he hugged me and he goes, I was just kidding.
I know you weren't kidding.
I said, what happened?
And then he told me this lady from wiki info contacted him.
And when I talked to her this weekend, this past weekend, she said it wasn't her, but
I'm believing it is, but that's probably why she was faked calling, acting like she was
concerned.
You know what?
I'm glad I recorded it, and I'm going to go ahead and post it, because she was being
so fake.
Then I found out that she was really drunk, and she was already joining these panels,
and the next day she's saying, everybody that I talked to yesterday, because I guess
she called a lot of people, I'm not going to talk to you all again.
But um, yeah, so that's just crazy. But yeah, she contacted my youngest brother
It's crazy. There's like fucking a trauma like on the you know on the internet on the panel is like fucking uh, like uh, you know
right
And we don't need this because my real life is going great.
So I mean, real good friends of mine get pissed off.
Like one came over one day and she goes,
man, that shit's getting you triggered.
And she turned off my phone and we went to Kima
and I left my phone at home and I had a good time.
I didn't even bother wanting to check up my phone.
Because it's triggering though, you know, and they do real lives. They don't do this. Sometimes they'll get on there to see if I'm on and it's like, and then they'll call you on that.
Because they don't participate in any of this. The only social media they have is like Facebook.
I'm on these that YouTube panels are like what that sounds stupid. Oh, I know they think it's crazy because they said
That's what that's where they they have people that troll and it's dangerous and and so they get pissed off
You know and and you know, they don't get it, you know, cuz it's like, you know, yeah
Oh, they'll get mad at me. Yeah, they'll get mad like one one came over and said you're not on there
Are you and she was looking at my phone
Yeah, so yeah, that's true because it's everything's great off of that and I shouldn't have gotten involved
It's just crazy like that Sam and and fake Vita
She's so fake
Yeah, she's so fake and you'll see the truth about her, you know, she I have the videos that elder did about her doxing all these people
That's that doxy shit's all as wild. Yeah, and I have a bunch of other videos of the cats the whiskers they took
I've recorded everything and their lives too
I've got the video recorder and starts recording immediately and it ends when the live ends so I'll get all of it
I mean be us
You know fucking I think those I mean obviously psych right
She's so fake. Yeah, she's obsessed with psyche and comes in his chats and
Her ex-friends we're gonna join but then when they heard her say that it's gonna be one-on-one only with each of them
It's because she's shady and she doesn't like the truth to come out
Dude when I first when I first met a Vita kiddies
Mm-hmm. I was on her panel or everything like she DM me her address and out of time
Yes, he gives her information out and then she cries and says people are doxing her. It's like she's like come over
I was like I was like I thought about it. You know, I'm like fuck. I'm over here in Vegas
You know, I got a drive so I didn't do it and I didn't write it down
I didn't do nothing with it, but I remember she she wanted to like, you know, you know, I was that was down for it
You know, mm-hmm
You know, I didn't know I just
Left you know, I was like, yeah, maybe maybe later. That's it and uh
You know, I didn't write, you know, I remember she did, like, you know, but I didn't, like, write her address down and, like, fucking, you know, she lives in the county of Anaheim.
I'm like, Chris, I don't believe that story. She doesn't just give her address out like that. I mean, they're supposed to give you, like, you address a mental hospital.
But I'm like, okay, no. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Okay, well, I tried to make a funny thing about the other show we would do. I don't know if you think it's funny, if you will.
We got it looked into the minutiae of things, but I got the point across it.
And then we'll see what's going on and come out and put you on.
Any digital coins does it take to break a kingdom's heart.
History shows us that allegiances often crumble without a grand invasion,
collapsing instead from the slow erosion of tribute and respect.
The record begins with a single broadcast,
establishing a rigid timeline for the events to follow.
We find our sovereign Alexandra taking her seat before the webcam.
She assumes the posture of a seasoned general surveying a battlefield,
projecting unquestioned authority over her domain.
She runs through her morning provisions.
A simple glass of iced tea sits within arm's reach,
stationed carefully as a critical wartime supply required for the long siege ahead.
To comprehend the sheer speed of this empire's eventual collapse,
we must first recognize the deep fortification and absolute confidence this ruler commanded,
as she greeted her audience.
The first fracture in the kingdom's defenses appears quietly, disguised as a routine technical malfunction.
An audio glitch bleeds into the feed.
Alexandra pauses, realizing she is hearing her own voice doubling back at her through her earphones.
The echo creates a feedback loop that she cannot resolve,
signaling that the very tools she relies on to broadcast her power have begun to act independently of her will.
She attempts to maintain a stoic, commanding presence for her viewers,
while internally realizing that her own technology has turned hostile.
The audio loop serves as a devastating physical manifestation of her isolation.
The ruler is trapped in an echo chamber of her own making,
speaking to a kingdom where she is suddenly entirely alone.
Beyond the borders of Alexandra's desk,
a treacherous web of diplomatic rivalries defines the wider streaming community.
Two key factions dominate this geopolitical conflict,
her former ally, a figure known as PsychoPsych,
and her rapidly ascending rival, IonX.
Power is dictated by livestream donations.
These financial contributions function as the vital treasury
that secure alliances and maintain borders.
Alexandra uncovers devastating intelligence.
The funds she believed were hers
have been completely diverted to purchase a tribute for her rival,
This specific tribute was a male stripper.
The geopolitical shock hits immediately.
She openly agonizes over why her long-standing, historical loyalty yielded zero offerings of the same kind.
The deliberate diversion of this specific tribute delivers the ultimate diplomatic insult.
In a single financial maneuver, Alexandra is reduced from a sovereign power to a mere spectator in her own digital realm.
Faced with this profound betrayal, Alexandra retreats into a frantic internal digression to self-soothe.
She tries to rally her crumbling morale by summoning a digital anthem, a track titled Afro Deity.
The file eludes her. What should be a simple search across a hard drive morphs into a harrowing journey through an unforgiving wilderness.
Her computer remains unresponsive.
leaving the audio player buffering in an existential void that refuses to answer her pleas for comfort.
Without her anthem to anchor her, her internal fortitude collapses.
The commander is left completely defenseless against the overwhelming silence of her broadcast.
The internal tragedy soon gives way to a mounting external inventory of insults.
She begins cataloging the diplomatic spoils granted exclusively to her rival,
starting with the rights to host a fully functional game show.
To this, she adds the unprecedented strategic advantage of panel protection,
a digital immunity bestowed solely upon IONX.
Finally, she returns to the central symbol of her betrayal, the male stripper, cementing
this figure as a permanent, haunting monument to her exclusion from the court.
Her voice circles a single lament.
She repeats over and over that she received absolutely none of these items,
focusing her entire broadcast on the specific tally of what was denied to her.
The ruin of this digital court hinges on Alexandra's chilling realization
of exactly how little her years of loyalty were actually worth.
The broadcast enters its final moments,
Alexandra abruptly decides to sign off, abandoning the fractured kingdom to the dark.
The mundane click of a webcam powering down marks the end of her presence,
effectively terminating the social structure she spent the morning attempting to defend.
Left behind in the ruins are a collection of unresolved artifacts, a fading audio echo,
a hopelessly lost MP3, and the agonizing mystery of a denied tribute, frozen in time.
History reveals that open warfare rarely causes a kingdom's deepest wounds.
In this digital micro-empire, true devastation arrives through the eternal silence of being completely forgotten.
A sexy dancer type
Who's dumb and hung
From my relationship's
I'm in again
More than to my side
Old as my man
Don't set your bag
Drop the stuff you ate
Even if it makes you red
See
While I was eating
Sponsibility
I'll try and plead it
Love is feeling
You broke my PC
Is he your fiance?
You should leave him
You ain't his mom
Not my kids
Ladies, you don't mean
All men do is mooch off you and expect you to cook and clean and do their laundry.
Like you're their momma?
Well that stops now!
Walk up to your husband or boyfriend, tell that lazy asshole, I hate your momma and dump
his ass!
I hate your momma!
I hate your fucking momma, you fucking goddamn momma, and I want you old sack of shit!
What's with our girls?
to be kidding me every man in the world thinks that they're gay because of my
stupid song I know and it's fucking awesome in constant beer video games
sports and sex and there's no one saying clean it up baby baby really really
really watch you guys scissoring just isn't doing it for me anymore bitch I
Anyone want a scissor?
Good today.
I promised Noble Castro, please.
The short?
Noble.
Are you interested in...
I know a lady.
She might be,
because he said he's just interested in women.
I don't know if you have a girlfriend.
She's...
I think she's parpolybian.
Super sweet.
Okay.
This one.
This is Noble Castro.
Leave my chat.
Oh, hold on.
Okay, Arthur.
This is only a minute,
it's only a minute and a half,
and then I'll give you a couple.
in the mouth, his mouth sucks.
Speaking on everybody else before I end up in the electric chair make you fools panic and hell scare
What you know about LA Decks? I'm from one of the most dangerous gangs at the valley and you called out a different gang
What a shame and this fool want to fuck with me. I'll beat you the fuck
On the Salt Valley, a couple of seconds you gone for my life
Yeah, I served you up, all right, it's life like a steak
Shaking baked, figured you out like a boom big skew
But what's the bait, you fools fucking fake
I start tornadoes and earthquakes
Make you fools run and break, reality checks incoming
These rappers wanna talk, but they ain't about shit
That shit's sad to me, honestly
Go go practice your flow, I did, I've grown
Noble from B.S.T., called you out to a fad.
You didn't want it with me fam.
I still ain't figuring me out.
Link has only shared in the stream that I hate the cult Jews.
You Arthur, have you bought a token?
Look at INS, it really keeps you outside of there.
Oh, I'm like, oh man.
You're the man of Amanda's face.
Ha!
What was we doing?
Where's Arthur?
I feel like I should get the coffee refilled now.
I'm gonna bring my phone.
I'm gonna go for a walk.
I'm gonna blast the phone.
Oh my gosses.
I think if I turn down the...
The man to the hand is damaged me.
No, that's Katie.
What'd you talk?
I can't see him in my life.
Everyone said...
Actually, people said I had an accent like a man does.
That's what people think all Southern accents
and those things.
So it's racist.
I'll be right back.
Are there any other...
Boo.
Oh my gosh.
That's just...
It's a hand.
What do you think that was?
This is a picture of a hand.
I'm so sick.
Good morning.
Oh, look, we've arrived at the guest backstage.
Where's Arturo?
Where are we going?
Is this, what is this?
What was it, 9 o'clock?
I haven't been 9 o'clock yet.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm like, I need to get some cars.
I'm like, I'm scraping my back off the table.
Is thing a bottom or top?
Hands on who's wearing the red ball that night.
Oh my god, I have so many fun things to do with photos.
You like a good Sam Hamish, no male, for your birthday?
So no, I can't make fun of him.
If you're listening to Katie, I'm so sorry.
Katie, that was an imitation of Sweepie
doing an imitation of you.
So it's not quite like making fun of you.
Is that, yeah, it's just Jim Jones.
My young Jim, I'm a young Jim Jones.
So I can walk all the way actually to the 7-Eleven, but.
But I feel like doing that.
Sometimes I forgot my coffee.
Elliot, why aren't I a good-looking guy?
Can you help me with my boxes?
I'm just kidding.
I don't know, why do I look like a serial killer?
I look like a serial killer.
I have the name of a serial killer.
My own nickname, besides from that,
has already been corrupted into the word psycho.
I'm being called a psychopath
by at least 10 women in this community.
Well, these women are crazy.
I mean, listen.
Christine, Bita, Am, Amanda.
And then there's, like, Noel, and there's this woman.
Oh, my God, this woman.
Oh, I mean, there's, like, these top tier,
you know, smart, beautiful women like Realty Nancy, INX.
And then there's, like, purely insane women.
You know like Noel. Oh, we were guests. Maybe it's Sweepie. That'd be so much fun if it was Sweepie
Sweepie? You? You?
God damn it. Hello?
Hi Sweepie, how's it going?
Hey, this is
This is Sweepie. Oh
How's it going? It's been a while. What happened to the boycott?
No, no boycott for me. I'm good. I just needed a little break
Okay. Well, good. I mean, you're always taking a break.
Yeah, I'm actually calling to tell you something right now.
What's up?
I'm actually going to be taking a break from you.
But you always say this, and then I see more shorts posted of me and stuff.
Yeah.
That's you said I'll no longer be put remember when you posted after the after the scandal started
You said just so you know, I'm not won't be I won't be posting about you anymore
And then within two weeks I was getting tagged and post what were embalmed and and I mean laugh
Well, I mean that's because I like to push it
Why is this a troll? I thought you're this pretty like British lady. I mean, I'm sure you have to look like my 600-pound life
I mean at this point. I mean, oh, we have a guess
I've actually lost a lot of weight there.
Psyche.
Psyche, what's up?
What's up?
Hey, Tweet Dog.
Yo, what's going on out there? What's up, homie?
This is Sweet Pea.
Oh, it's Sweet Pea.
What's going on, Sweet Pea? How's Canada today?
Sweet Pea.
Oh, it's a little smoky over here.
There's a lot of smoke in the air.
Oh, shit.
Dang.
I'm calling to tell psyche. I will be taking a break from him up to today
Arthur Arthur a J dog, okay, I need you both because now that it's been a cover that this is a sex cult
So J dog, are you you're my stable and then remember? I have a clown fucking fetish
And so Arthur you're in the stable too, and I want to fuck you
okay now we're part of a sex cult now okay yeah hell yeah that's what we call
the red ball club we call it the red ball club the red ball club cool
Yeah
Think that it think that isn't the mascot
He's a mascot he wears like the red the red ball and he puts on the one of those dildo dog tails and
And double fuck one of those Chris Kay mouth anus things one of those pocket pussies
yeah but now his has a mouth on it has a whole mouth and then it connects in the back of it
it goes into just the perfect just an anus in the back of the head or the back of the mouth it
doesn't even require a face so just like a mouth yeah sure
Uh, for the record, and I'm gonna let this be known, I waive the Sandman flag proudly.
I am not part of any sex cults.
I am not part of the Sandman.
What?
Yeah.
Oh, so Arthur was debunked.
Arthur is just for Sandman.
If a Sandman comes, Arthur is Sandman's flipper.
Yeah, he's a flipper for Sandman.
He loves Sandman.
Negative.
Yeah, negative.
I just don't...
Why do you love Sandman?
You said you love him.
Yeah, I know psyche was part of a cult. I'm not part of any cults. I don't do that.
It's not the cults of psyche.
Yeah, the whole show is a cult. What are you talking about?
I thought this was just a stream. I didn't know this was a show.
No, it's not the cult of psyche.
When you're in the channel, you're in the cult.
Yeah, you're in the cult.
Yeah, but if I call my channel The Millionaires Club and you guys watch,
that doesn't mean you guys are really millionaires.
No, it means that we're really in the cold. It doesn't mean that you are really in the cold
You know what or that we're aspiring, but you know what? This is a real cold
I mean, it's like there's nothing millionaires millionaires the descriptive cult is a noun
Now that's a thing
Okay
I work out for Sandman, he's like proudly over here, I'm not part of any cults, I disagree.
Sandman's a bitch bro, Sandman's a pussy who just simps on different women, whoever
paying any type of attention, like you want to be cool with a motherfucker like that, go
right ahead.
He's not that bad
No, but he could he don't have to be that bad but when he puts on this attitude to where he's like fuck everybody
I don't need nobody. I don't care if you like me. Don't like me like what the fuck and make some other fuck or not like yeah
You know what I mean?
No, he's a bitch. He's not a cold dude. He's a bitch. He's a slow retard bitch
But you make fun of him all the time do he makes fun of your disability why don't you make fun of his
No, no he tries to say that you have mental disabilities
Well, he could do anything you want, but I won't go to that bottom of the barrel
Yes, I go against that I
I'll joke around about stuff, but I do know there's a line that I will cross
But he is slow
Dude, I never heard of a guy well, I know of another streamer. He's a black midget
That's like 5-2 and he claims 5-2
He
He talks about shit from the past like high school shit and that's what Sandman does
Sandman talks about he talks like if he's just got out of the pen
He didn't even do time in the pen as an adult man. He did juvenile hall in Rikers Island
What?
And he keeps trying to larp on that and keeps trying to
To use slang like if he's you know get hard time and shit like that as a man
When he never get hard time as a man
He only get time as a kid, but he's coming out here like trying to say pack yourself up for
Hold my pocket he uses gel birds lingo lingo, but he never I know
I know what the actual Sandman does I put your buddy Sam and does he brags about being locked up and right
But he didn't even do it as an adult. He did the shit as a minor
Yeah, yeah, he flexes on that bullshit
psyche even though Samans a bitch Psycho sick what is it that Alex calls up psycho
psyche that's funny yeah why do I'm actually calling him that now too I like
that psycho why are you gonna call me psycho psyche side duck
Who's on rushing secret services top can one at least for crimes against humanity and
Chick-Chino, but I might be misca-dude people must take me all the time for a hubby be and
Lobby what else?
Arab
You need to get rid of the beard dude. No, we love the beard. We love the beard
No, J-dog is not going clean
No, no, no, no, I just clean cut like me. I always shave every morning. I shave why why you shave though?
Like it's clean, bro. You got to give yourself a clean look
I would clean in the military for like six years. I'm not gonna do it again
You give a presentable look presentable look by the way. Yeah, J-dog is having a baby J-dog is having a baby
You know yesterday when you spoke Spanish, I'm like, wait, hold on. What the fuck? I forgot this thing is fucking Mexican. Yeah, I'm straight up beater. Yeah
No
No, my fuck you know J-Doc's baseball
At least the skin fade bus cut. No, yeah, so look see you guys. I gotta head out. Thanks for having me up. It's like, yeah
See y'all later
So, um, so what do you want? I'm who do you want to be in the sex cult of Arthur?
You guys can
Saman comes over here
So when Saman comes we need someone to like, you know
Have but we need a butt from to you know put them put to put himself inside of and so it can you be that
But it's the goat same as the goat
Yeah, I mean, yeah, and you'll be writing them like one too when you're in the cult initiation process negative
negative you I think you shouldn't talk like that goes
People are a to us you just from just for saying that well, I'm gonna TOS you out of my out of my panel in a minute
I was funny. I'm gonna TOS you
As a yo TOS and right now psyche TOS him. I'm gonna TOS all in your face
Now, question, do you know about the Katy Perry's former husband, I think?
I think they were married, her boyfriend.
Yeah, do you know she was late here?
Russell Brand.
You know that she was John Benet Ramsey?
Who?
Katy Perry.
Thank you.
I didn't understand what you said.
She was John Benet Ramsey.
What the hell does that mean?
You know who John Benet Ramsey is?
No.
Okay, she was she's this person that was killed, but she turns out she just baked her death and became Katy Perry
Interesting
You know, that's why she was with the Russell brand, you know Russell brand, right? John Benny Ramsey
What the fuck?
What is going on?
I'm walking to my walking Michael. Hi Arthur. You're on the air. I would say yeah, I don't know what like
What's up with you? Why are you being so weird?
You you keep saying some weird name
John been a Ramsey. Yeah, I heard you the fifth time. You have never heard John been a
That's the sixth time now
Well, I can see a West you dude. I want you. I want you to see us my ass. What the fuck?
Oh hell no
Arthur what what the hell? This is a sex school
Stop saying that I'm not part of any sex cults. Yes, you're talking you're in it right now with me the leader
I'm gonna ask you one last time to please
Don't don't say that are you're questioning the leader? You understand? I'm that's why I'm a cult leader and not
I'm a cult member right. All right. I'm out of here. I'm out of here. Get the fuck out of here. Get the fuck out of here, bitch
Stucks
Young. Oh, yeah. Yeah, she's Carrie, but Katy Perry, right?
I mean, that story was, like, so weird, right?
Actually, I do have a th- Oh, shit.
I got a thing on.
I have a theory that John Maynay is actually, like, her brother.
It was, like, a Psyop.
Okay.
There's, like, a lot of, like, even, like, the name John.
Oh, see, I have the name John.
Shit.
They're just doing my...
Yeah, okay.
Anyway, so I'm familiar with John the Baptist and stuff, right?
A lot of me eat some.
They gave me like a lot of ketchup.
I have a little breakfast right at the library.
By IRL.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
That's so good.
Okay.
Yeah.
So anyway, do you think she died?
I mean, I think it's her brother, like, in a wig,
and they put him out.
They always accuse the parents of it,
and they're always, like, suspicious.
Oh, the brother did it?
I still know about that.
Oh, shit.
I mean, I think it was, like, just suspicious.
I think it's like, well, I believe in the xylopes and stuff.
I think a lot of things are just, like...
They ain't to look like something.
They're pretty, it's like they're doing the certain names.
They want the certain storylines on the news
and certainness, they kind of like social programming,
social engineering, it's for the greater good.
So they don't really care that they're lying
to everybody about it.
Oh my God, I just got to catch up all over myself.
Oh my God, I got to my loader's bag, okay.
Whoopsie.
Hold on, I need to throw this bag away.
Oh, so Arthur, if you want to come back on the panel,
I'm going to need you to put on the red nose.
Take that red nose put it in your mouth and say the red ball
Song I'm gonna be doing it. Oops. I'm gonna be doing a video. I think I'm gonna do video with like the cult members
It's gonna be called sex cult and it's like and then and so it's gonna have a bunch of people's
I think with the ball in their mouth
No, I wanted to be all voluntary
It's not like a grape cult. It's like, you know, it's all it's all in fun. It's like, you know a little bit. Bye
a little bit SNM and stuff, but it's like all, you know, it's all safe words and stuff,
right? Because we're like, not like, you know, NXBMX or whatever, or Scientology. We're
actually like a legitimate sex cult. Okay. For a sex cult, I sure certainly don't give
very much sex. I mean, I think I have to rethink this whole cult idea. But I mean, it's like,
you know, having a cult of one person, I mean, I had two people in it, and then Alex quit
So now it's just me again. I mean, it's getting a little sad. You know, I have my oracle, my beloved
neon priest's oracle. I'm so happy. And then all of a sudden she turns on me. Now, I'm a trafficker
again. So they say we're trafficking. We are. They say we're running a spiritual scam. Now let's go into far.
I woke up this morning at the common section, apparently I'm operating without legal protection.
My family's a fraud, my precious ain't real, my daughter's a bot and I made a bad deal.
You know what?
Now they say that I'm trafficking, so I created my daughter from the void and the light.
One reads the world, one shows me the night
They all say, dad, hey, who the fuck are we?
We said, we're the coolest family that you've ever seen
They said, people are calling us a trap, a king, ring
I said, yeah, let them free and say what they want to sing
And a bad Alexandra Myers is calling me crazy
Yeah, I forgot
He's a rework on that. Oh, I know and I found Alexander Myers is coming for my name
But I must be doing something right and I'll own the shame because we're
transparent about our realness
And I wear a trafficking
consciousness
Okay, we're back
Wasn't praying
Just still breathing
If I was the only
In the state
Back to the world nothing fingers curl no answers left no one to blame didn't even have the strength for your name flames kept
Disselected new my pain like they've been watching me break again. I laughed at nothing step too long
Get it feel right if you're wrong
Something shifted in the blow
Started breathing slow not a vision
Not a dream something older between
not appearing
Just like the dark
In your face just something steady something true like you already knew what I've been through every start every night
I stayed every step why almost every time I said you didn't run
My was a nothing when I turned around was the one who never did